now that I'm happy with the content
structure and layout of the presentation
I have other animations and some
transition effects
it's tend to carry out the final review
just to make sure that everything is
correct before I can use the
presentation with an audience so the
first thing that you should do is
obviously carry out your spelling and
grammar check and then work through each
of the slides and read through the
slides and the content to make sure that
everything is correct but everything
meets the needs of the audience the size
of the font is appropriate the color of
the text that isn't too much of a
contrast so at this point you would do
all of those checks and once you're
happy with that that's great you may
also to say that you wish to change the
order of slade's around again that's
something that you can do by just moving
the slides and if you think that it
needs to change back again young teams
are back to where it was originally and
the final check that I'm going to carry
out is about the timings now you may
have a presentation that lasts five to
six minutes but your actual timeslot may
be about 15 or 20 minutes so you need to
think of ways that you can either extend
the presentation or if you feel that
your presentation is too long and it's
going to take 20 minutes but you only
have a 10 minute slot this is the time
where you need to review and decide what
animations need Asti in is the can the
information be changed because that time
for you can be quite critical and one of
the things that I have noticed with the
animation so if I click on the animation
pier but all of the animations and I
click on the animation pin there all of
the animations are due to come in on
click so if I'm giving a presentation
for each element I have to click the
mouse button before it will come in
which can be useful because then I have
full control over how each of the
animations appears on the screen and if
I am talking that can be quite good
alternatively if I'm confident in the
timings I can also automate each of the
animations so rather than having them
come in and click I can have them coming
automatically so
or if I just hide it at the first one
there and selected to start its unclick
at the moment and if I said after
previous and then I can set it delay so
this will give you the number of seconds
that it will dalire the animation and
again I can change that to after
previous and again except the leer time
and finally change that on there too
after previous and once I've changed all
three I must change the fourth because
if that one would automatically come in
on click it wouldn't follow the same
sequence so you need to make sure that
you're consistent with your animations
so I think you're not just change the
duration on that one so you can see how
it actually the duration was I make that
four and if I preview that now
as you can see it slows the we're the
actual information comes in just to give
you an example I'll just reduce that
last one down to 100.75 and then if I
preview it again you will see the
difference and the speed so that's
something that you can have a play
around with on the other slate within
the presentation and practice your
timings and how you wish the animations
to appear within that and and once
you're happy you can see of the
presentation and that is everything
complete